"The Missing Piece"
(Episode 9)
Why don't I draw Zhou Yang?
Or maybe I'll draw you.
You just love this sofa bed.
You won't even sleep with me.
Your right hand is badly hurt.
There may be lasting effects.
It could affect your daily life.
Please prepare yourself mentally.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Ah.
I
I'm just cleaning up.
Why are you crying?
Oh.
I probably slept too much this afternoon.
I'm fine.
It hurts.
It's probably just that my
hand hasn't fully healed yet.
Once it heals, I'll be fine.
Even if it never fully heals, it's okay.
Worst case, I just stop drawing.
I'll just get a different job then.
Insurance or sales.
I might even earn more.
You can't hold the brush anymore?
Mm.
I'm here for you.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
Come on, Shen Mo.
You can do it.
So I won't be a burden to Yang.
Hello.
And you are?
I'm the one who contacted you online.
Here to apply for the
painting teacher position.
Did you bring your resume?
Shen Mo.
Your resume is really impressive.
No, no, not at all.
Ah.
So you've been trained
since childhood, right?
I've been learning to
paint since I was little.
And I kept doing part-time
work through college.
So I'm pretty experienced.
Take a look at my paintings.
Oh wow.
This is really well done.
Formally trained.
And you draw this well.
Hey.
What made you think of my little studio?
I haven't worked since I graduated.
My partner's been
supporting me this whole time.
He leaves early and comes home late.
It kind of hurts me
I want to...
help share the load.
Mm.
Got it.
But the pay here isn't great.
Ah.
That's fine, that's fine.
In that case.
Just do a quick sketch first.
And I'll take a look at your basic skills.
Uh.
What is it?
Is it a bad time?
Well.
I hurt my hand a while back.
Ah.
It's fine.
Just draw something simple
I'll just get the gist.
We only teach little kids here.
As long as you're decent, it's fine.
Hey.
Shen Mo, what are you...?
After I hurt my hand.
I can't grip a brush anymore.
You can't even grip it this much?
I've tried so many times.
Not really.
Ah.
How long till it heals?
I don't know either.
Oh boy.
Then there's nothing I can do.
If you can't paint
I can't hire you even if I want to.
Boss, don't worry.
Whether it's skill or ability
I can do it all.
Whether you want me to teach or paint
I can teach anything
I can do anything too.
I believe in your skill
I believe in your teaching too.
But you can't paint right now.
What about when the kids need a demo piece?
I can't exactly tell the kids
the teacher can't paint.
That just doesn't make sense.
I've already sent out so many resumes.
Please, boss
I'm really sorry.
My hands are tied too.
Try your best.
Go get your hand checked first.
How about this?
Once your hand is better, contact me anytime.
Alright.
Thanks, boss.
Ah.
[Desperately searching
for library shelvers]
Shen Mo.
Mr. Ji.
Found him.
Good.
Little Shen.
Work faster.
You're so young.
Ah.
Got it, boss.
Shen Mo.
What are you doing here?
I got a job as a library shelver.
Today's my first trial day.
Why didn't you tell me you were going out?
Huh?
Did you think I'd gone missing?
You've been looking for me all along.
You're still not over your illness.
What if you wandered off
and something happened?
Oh, come on.
It's fine.
How could I ever bear
to leave you alone?
Why do you want to do this?
I just thought
I could help out with the family bills.
Silly.
We don't need you doing this.
Does this go here?
Ah.
Yeah.
These.
These is all my work,
I can handle it myself.
Our boss is watching the whole time.
Let me do it.
Go home and wait for me.
Mm.
Don't worry.
Okay.
You're off work so early today.
How was it?
Was work tiring today?
Not too bad.
Uh.
You don't have to work on weekends, right?
Nope.
What's up?
Wanna go to an art show this weekend?
My friend just gave me two tickets.
Whoa.
Did your friend give you the tickets?
Or did you know I wanted to go
and asked a friend for them on purpose?
Just tell me, are you coming or not?
Yes yes yes.
As long as I'm with you.
Anywhere is fine.
Look at this.
Whoa.
Seeing those paintings by the masters...
they're really amazing.
I've seen your paintings.
You paint really well too.
How could I compare to them?
Quit your library job.
Why?
Have you ever seen a master
who works in a library?
Suffering is the breeding
ground for creativity.
I would never let you suffer.
Once we get your hand fixed
keep painting
until you're better than all of them.
So once I become a great painter
and start making money,
I'll buy you that big
house across the street.
Okay.
Then I'll hold my art show right here
and you just wait for me
at home like a good boy.
Okay.
Then I'll wait for you to come home.
All contract documents in this batch
strictly follow the group's
three-tier review process.
First, the department
head does the initial review,
checking the data
and the plan's feasibility.
Then the deputy GM reviews and confirms
to control project and funding risks.
Finally, Legal
and Risk Control do a
double compliance check
to verify...
Mr. Ji.
Is something wrong with my plan?
No, no.
Just go with your plan.
Meeting adjourned.
Mr. Ji
I was just about to get your signature.
No time.
Some other day
I'm going to the hospital.
Huh? What are you sick with?
I'm not sick
I'm visiting a patient.
I've never seen Mr. Ji like this.
Yeah.
Feels like he's in love.
Don't worry about that.
I got you the best
hospital and specialists here.
This hand repair surgery of yours...
It'll be fine for sure.
Mm.
What if it can't be cured?
What if the surgery fails?
What if it gets worse?
Don't be scared.
It'll be fine for sure.
No matter what happens.
I'll be right by your side.
I lied.
I'm not scared at all.
If it works, great.
If it fails, no regrets.
Besides.
As long as you're by my side
I'm not afraid of anything.
Sometimes I really can't figure you out.
Mm?
So soft-tempered, like
anyone can push you around.
But once you dig in your heels.
You're stubborn as hell.
Is that a compliment or an insult?
Guess.
Alright.
Don't be so nervous.
By this time tomorrow,
the surgery will be over.
It's nothing.
I just don't like hospitals much.
My mother...
Mm?
Let's talk about that later.
You should get some rest today.
The surgery is tomorrow.
[Operation on-going]
Doctor.
How was it?
Was the surgery successful?
Very successful.
Hang in there.
The surgery went great.
You'll be out of here soon.
Before the anesthesia, I'd already decided.
If the surgery failed,
worst case, you can be my right hand.
Don't talk nonsense.
Once you're discharged,
I'll take you out for something good.
Okay.
Wow.
So much food.
It all looks so delicious.
Of course.
This is my secret spot.
I usually
don't bring just anyone here.
Such a great place.
Who have you been bringing here?
Yang.
You'd better come clean.
Let me run something by you.
Starting today, you're living with me
I already found the place.
Why?
Isn't our place now pretty good?
You'll like our new home even more.
So where exactly is our new home?
This...
Isn't this...
Yep.
So you can become a great painter sooner.
Of course we should live near the gallery.
But.
This must cost a fortune.
Such a nice neighborhood.
And didn't you say back then
that you were giving it to me?
This is an investment.
You're a future great painter.
Okay.
Then I, the great painter Shen.
For my comeback piece
I'll paint you first, okay.
Or maybe a Ferris wheel.
Ferris wheel?
Yeah.
Near your old rental place.
Isn't there a big Ferris wheel?
I won you over right
under that Ferris wheel.
Don't move.
Your hand's not healed yet.
Thanks for your effort.
Did you forget something?
Hmm?
Give me your hand.
Yang.
Do you think my hand can still heal?
Of course.
As long as you keep at it.
It'll pay off for sure.
It definitely will.
Okay.
Then once my hand heals,
I want to turn that empty south-facing room
into a studio.
And fill it with all my paintings.
By then, that one of
the Ferris wheel will go right in the center.
So you'll see it right away.
Okay.
Mm.
Then I'll just paint at home.
Cook for you at home.
And sing for you too.
We'll plan where to travel together.
Sounds good.
I've got to find a chance to devour you.
Merry Christmas.
During the New Year,
I'm planning to go abroad to see my family.
Okay.
Alright.
Then I'll just wait for you to come back.
What about you?
Are you home alone or going back
to your hometown for New Year's?
It's fine
I'll just go back to my hometown.
Don't worry about me.
Merry Christmas.
I miss you.
Stop it.
Yang.
I'm not Zhou Yang.
You're the one I love the most.
How could I be wrong?
You're still not well.
I was never sick.
We'll continue when you're better.
Hey.
What are you up to?
I'm alone...
I'm home cleaning.
Weren't you going back home?
It's close
I'll leave once I'm done.
Ugh.
Yang, don't worry about me.
Just stay abroad with your family.
Mm.
Remember to put medicine on your hand.
Don't worry.
Okay
I'm hanging up then.
Almost blew it.
Are you asleep?
Not asleep yet.
Waiting for midnight.
You?
Still having dinner.
Oh right.
We're in different time zones.
Is it fun spending New Year abroad?
Nothing special.
Mo.
Where are you now?
I'm home.
Alone?
I went back to my hometown.
My parents are both here.
Mo.
Happy New Year.
Yang.
What are you doing right now?